B. AUSTIN RIGGS

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven software developer dedicated to continual skillset improvement. Pursuing a growing understanding of core programming concepts and familiarity with a wide-range of languages and concepts. Recent experience working as part of a Scrum Team and working with front end, back end, and database languages.

WEBSITE, LINKEDIN, GITHUB

- http://bariggs15.github.io
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/baustinriggs
- https://github.com/bariggs15

SKILLS

- C#/MVC/Entity
 Frameworks, ASP.NET
- HTML5, CSS3
- Javascript/jQuery
- SQL/MySQL, MySQL Server
- Visual Studio IDE
- Agile/Scrum

• Git/GitHub

EXPERIENCE

DOCTOR OF PHYSICAL THERAPY 05/2016 to Current

Self Employed, Tulsa, OK

- Managed quality assurance program, including on-site evaluations, internal audits and customer surveys.
- Communicated with physicians to provide updates on patient care.
- Assessed treatment plans and made adjustments as needed for maximum benefits.
- Documented each patient case with updates in computer system.
- Provided personalized in-home therapeutic treatments to patients after hospitalization

SAFETY ENGINEER 2012 to 2012

BS&B Safety Systems, Tulsa, OK

- Updated digital manuals and company logs to current standards and practices.
- Upon assessment, created optional solutions (via PowerPoint and Word Documents) for upper management and presented on regular basis.
- Reviewed production work processes to detect possible safety concerns, drafting corrective measures where appropriate.

INDUSTRIAL ENGINEER 2011 to 2011

Spirit Aerosystems, Tulsa, OK

- Designed improvements to equipment to optimize worker productivity.
- Reviewed and revised production schedules and engineering specifications.
- Identified problems and recommended new processes to improve efficiency and reduce costs.

EDUCATION

Tech Academy, Portland, OR

Graduate, Software Development, 04/2021

Southwest Baptist University, Bolivar, MO

Doctorate of Physical Therapy, Physical Therapy, 05/2016

Oklahoma State University, Stillwater, OK

Bachelor of Science, Industrial Engineering and Management, 05/2012